# **Achievements**

### 1st in my Institute

I held the first ranking in my institute of all Departments

### technical final project

design electronic Hand sterilization to fight Covid & people counter with my friends

# Network Administrator, CCTV

Teams AID: Building an integrated network with server connectivity and set up cameras with my friends in my training month.

# Competences

Kurdish

Fluent: speak & writing

Arabic

Fluent: speak & writing

#### **English**

Advanced: speak & writing(B2)

# Contact

- ★ Frbil
- **C** 07508554158
- edrisahmed9639@gmail.com
- edrisyousef1996@hotmail.com
- in Edris. Ahmed
- @edrisahmed96
- **f** Edris Ahmed

# EDRIS MOHAMMED AHMAD

## **Profile**

### **Birthday** 1/1/1996

I'm an excellent multitasker and dedicated worker.
I'm a creative trained graphic designer and marketing specialist with professional experience, responsible, and hardworking person. I held the first ranking in my institute. I can work well both in a team environment as well as using my initiative. addition, Computers have always been my passion.

# Experience

### Reception, Erbil | 2021/Jun - 2022/Jan

Fomex hotel

assists with booking rooms, register and check guests in, confirm guest in-room purchases during check-out, verify guest's payment method, answer and direct incoming calls.

### IT technician, Erbil | 2020 - Nov

Noble private institute

diagnose, repair, and maintain hardware and software components to ensure the smooth running of computer systems.

### Graphic designer, online | 2020 - Present

Free lance

adobe photoshop, Market research, logo design, Image editing, brochure design, poster, flyers and business cards, Social Media Marketing.

### Accountant, Erbil | 2018/Feb - 2019

**FMM Market** 

Accounting and Supervising some workers, Manage account department, Sales promotion techniques

# Café manager, Sulaymaniyah | 2016/Jun - 2018

Havana café

Manage budgets, Maintain relationships with customers, Manage project information, Cafe entry planning

# Data Entry, Duhok | 2015 - 2016

IRC

entering data into computers, Gather data, Data analyses in the camps in Duhok

# **Skills**

#### **IT Skills**

Computer Skills Programming Processing information Networks



#### **General Skills**

Team work
Communication
Customer
service
Leadership
Problem-solving



### **Marketing Skils**

Social Media
Sales promotion
Outdoor
advertising



### **Education**

### Information Technology IT

Noble Institute, Erbil | 2019 - 2021

Computer Programming & Science, Advertising Techniques, Business intelligence, , Database, Networks, Graphic Design, Microsoft Office programs, computer hardware

## Keshka High School

Syria , Hasskah | 2010 - 2013 Completion of Assignments, Organizational Skills, Time Management

### Course

# FREE LANCER & SOCIAL MEDIA MARKETING

Gaza Sky Geeks, Erbil | 2021

Free work skills, Social media marketing, Business Process, compile content, work on online sites, Manage online content.

### GRAPHIC DESIGN & DIGITAL MARKETING

Smithson, Duhok | 2020

Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Illustrator, social media management, Digital Marketing techniques, Design graphics

#### DATA ANALYSIS

Point, Online | 2020

Analyze Data, work with Power BI program, Collect ICT data, analyze test data.

#### SOFT SKILLS COURSE

Parwin, Online | 2020

Time Management\_ Problem-Solving \_Some Communication Skills \_Computer Programs.

#### COMPUTER SKILLS AND PROGRAMS

Directorate of Vocational Training, Duhok | 2016 more than 150 hours of courses and training, How dealing with computer software and hardware.

# Referees

#### Ahmad N. Adil

, General manager(Noble) 0750 434 1606 Aahmednashwanl@gmail.com

#### Azad X. Ali

, Manager(FMM Market) 07503476171 azadali@gmail.com

#### Elham T. Yasin

, ASST .LECT(Noble) 07734020646 ilham.tahsin.93@gmail.com